robotentertainment.com 2018-10-23

# Robot Entertainment Privacy Policy | Robot Entertainment

Last Updated: 25 May 2018

Protecting your privacy is important to us. Accordingly, we're providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use our Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. So, please make sure that you have read and understand our Terms of Service. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we'll notify you of such changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we'll update the "Last Updated" date above to indicate when those changes will become effective. 

## How do we collect information?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services. 

## Information You Provide

_Account Information_

. If you create an Account we'll collect certain information that can be used to identify you, such as your user name, IP address, and email address (" **PII** "). We may also collect certain information that is not PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you, such as your country of residence. We may request additional information in the course of your use of the Services. 

_Community Participation_. When you use the Services to communicate with other users, whether by public forum posting, "personal message," in-game chat or other communication features available in the Games or community areas of our Sites, such communications are transmitted and stored by us. These communications are considered public and there is no expectation of privacy. We may monitor such communications and, by using the communication services in our Games and/or community areas of our Sites, you are indicating that you agree to such monitoring. 

_Note regarding international users_ : Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you're located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. 

_Note regarding children_ : Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible. 

## Information We Collect

_Information Collected Using Cookies and other Web Technologies_

. 

Like many website owners and operators, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies and Web Beacons to collection certain information. 

**"Cookies"** are small text files that are placed on your device by a Web server when you access our Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that you've logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use Cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent Cookies, session Cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don't accept Cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also place their own Cookies on your device. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of Cookies and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties. 

**"Web Beacons"** (also known as Web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that may be included on our Services for several purposes, including to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to track and measure the performance of our Services, to monitor how many visitors view our Services, and to monitor the effectiveness of our advertising. Unlike Cookies, which are stored on the user's device, Web Beacons are typically embedded invisibly on web pages (or in an e-mail). 

**"Log Data"** means the information our servers automatically record about how a person uses our Services, including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a " **User** "). Log Data may include information such as a User's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Services that a User clicked on and other statistics. We use Log Data to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) Log Data to improve, customize, and enhance the Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users' needs and preferences. 

_Location Information_. When you use our App we may collect and store information about your location by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation or by accessing your mobile device's GPS coordinates or coarse location if you enable location services on your device. We may use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. If you do not want us to collect location information, you may disable that feature on your mobile device. 

_Information Sent by Your Computer or Mobile Device_. We collect certain information that your computer or mobile device sends when you use our Services, like a device identifier, user settings and the operating system of your device, as well as information about your use of our Services. 

_Do Not Track_. Our Site does not have the capability to respond to "Do Not Track" signals received from various web browsers. 

## What Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

We will not share any PII that we have collected from you except as described below: 

_Information Shared with Our Services Providers_. We may engage third-party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services. For example, Xsolla provides our payment processing services. These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf and are expressly obligated not to disclose or use your PII for any other purpose. 

_Information Shared with Third Parties_. We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry research and analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes. 

_Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions_. Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. As a result, if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy or if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your PII may be disclosed or transferred to the third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction. 

_Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others_. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, warrants or court orders; (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and (iii) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

## The Security of Your Information

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information. Also be aware that as part of using our Services and interacting or playing with other users in our games or on our websites, part of your data may be visible to the other players, including your player name, in-game chats, your progress, and other in-game activities. 

## Links to Other Sites

Our Services may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we're not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access. 

## Your Choices

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your PII and we'll respect the choices you make. Please note that if you decide not to provide us with the PII that we request, you may not be able to access all of the features of the Services. 

_Opt-Out_. We may periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote our Services. When you receive such promotional communications from us, you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" (either through your Account or by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive). We do need to send you certain communications regarding the Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications — e.g., communications regarding updates to our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy or information about billing. 

_Accessing and Modifying Your Information_. You can access and modify the PII associated with your Account by accessing your user profile on the Services. If you want us to correct or deactivate your account you can contact us at [support@robotentertainment.com](mailto:support@robotentertainment.com) with your request. We'll take steps to deactivate your account (and/or delete your data) as soon as practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. If you request, we will provide you a copy of your personal data in an electronic format. If you wish to object about how we use or share your data, please contact us by emailing [support@robotentertainment.com](mailto:support@robotentertainment.com). 

## Data Portability

If you are a Data Subject in the European Economic Area (EEA), you retain at all times the right to exercise your right of having your Personal Data exported and transferred – in a safe way – to another provider of Services similar to ours. You may exercise this right by making a request, in accordance with Data Protection Laws, by emailing [support@robotentertainment.com](mailto:support@robotentertainment.com). Any request related to your rights above, will be handled within thirty (30) days from the moment we receive such request. In case you deem your rights to have been violated, or if you are dissatisfied with the way your requests were handled, you can lodge a complaint with the applicable data protection regulator for the EEA country in which you reside. 

## Comments? Questions?

If you have comments or questions about data protection, our Privacy Policy, or if you have any requests for resolving issues with your personal data, please contact us using these methods: 

Data Controller: Robot Entertainment, Inc. 

Our Address: Robot Entertainment, Inc. 5055 W Park Blvd, Ste 600, Plano, Texas, USA 75093 

Email Contact: [support@robotentertainment.com](mailto:support@robotentertainment.com)
